[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dax Shepard was a child actor.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which Channel Island was the 2001 movie The Others supposedly set?", "correct_answer": "Jersey", "incorrect_answers": ["Guernsey", "Sark", "Alderney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Judd Apatow produced this 1996 comedy, starring Jim Carrey and directed by Ben Stiller.", "correct_answer": "The Cable Guy", "incorrect_answers": ["Heavyweights", "Crossing the Bridge", "Ace Ventura"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Topic: Name the Videogame. Characters: Samanosuke Akechi, Princess Yuki,  Nobunaga. What is the right question?", "correct_answer": "What is Onimusha?", "incorrect_answers": ["What is Devil May Cry?", "What is Tenchu: Wrath of Heaven?", "What is Genji: Dawn of the Samurai?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie won the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture for 1984?", "correct_answer": "Bolero", "incorrect_answers": ["Sheena", "Where the Boys Are 84", "Rhinestone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the planet with the biggest number of natural satellites in the solar system?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Uranus", "Neptune", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nationality was mathematician and surveyor Radhanath Sikdar, who was the first person to measure the height of Everest?", "correct_answer": "Bengali-Indian", "incorrect_answers": ["Chinese", "Pakistani", "Tibetan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "German, Italian, French this language, are all official languages of Switzerland.", "correct_answer": "Romansh", "incorrect_answers": ["Catalan", "Flemish", "Suomi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elder mothers have higher chances of conceiving twins.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alan Rickman was not the first choice for the role of Severus Snape.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the Roman counterpart of the Greek god Zeus.", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Saturn", "none of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following groups of animals does helminthology study?", "correct_answer": "Parasitic worms", "incorrect_answers": ["External parasites", "Oviparous animals", "Symbiotic animal species"]}]